http://www.stonehambank.com/privacy/

Skip to main contentAdjust Contrast( Press C )Text Size( Press T )Sitemap( Press S )Accessibility Statement( Press A )Close Toolbar( Press Escape )AccessibilityOptionsPrivacy PolicyHomePrivacy PolicyJump to:Privacy PolicyOnline & Mobile Banking (OB) Agreement and Disclosure Terms and ConditionsE-Sign DisclosureText Message Terms of UseVerified by Visa Terms & ConditionsEqual Housing LenderConsumer Fee ScheduleFunds Availability DisclosureOnline Advertising Terms of UsePersonal Finance Terms and Conditions FACTSWHAT DOES STONEHAMBANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?Why?Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.What?The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:Social Security numberPayment historyTransaction or loss historyCredit historyCredit scoresOverdraft HistoryWhen you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.How?All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons StonehamBank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.Reasons we can share your personal informationDoes StonehamBank share?Can you limit this sharing?For our everyday business purposes – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureausYesNoFor our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to youYesNoFor joint marketing with other financial companiesYesNoFor our affiliates' everyday business purposes – information about your transactions and experiencesYesNoFor our affiliates' everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthinessNoWe don't shareFor non-affiliates to market to youNoWe don't shareFor affiliates to market to youYesYesQuestions?Call toll-free 888-402-2265 or go to www.stonehambank.comWho We Are Who is providing this notice?StonehamBank means StonehamBank - A Co-operative Bank.What We Do How does StonehamBank protect my personal information?To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.We also maintain other physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect this information and we limit access to information to those employees for whom access is appropriate.How does StonehamBank collect my personal information?We collect your personal information, for example, when youMake deposits or withdrawals from your accountGive us your employment historyApply for financingProvide your mortgage informationShow your driver's licenseWe also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.Why can't I limit all sharing?Federal law gives you the right to limit onlysharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthinessaffiliates from using your information to market to yousharing for non-affiliates to market to youState laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.Definitions AffiliatesCompanies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.Our affiliates include non-financial companies such as Stoneham Financial Insurance.Non-affiliatesCompanies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.StonehamBank does not share with non-affiliates so they can market to you.Joint MarketingA formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.Our joint marketing partners include securities broker-dealers, a credit card company and insurance agencies.Other Important InformationWe will not share personal information from deposit or share relationships with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint marketing – without your authorization.
